DR.AH BALOCH

Professor of Anatomy



ABOUT ME

I am certified Microsoft innovative education expert (MIEE 2020-21), an enthusiastic and dedicated academician & researcher with extensive national and international experience across all branches of Human Anatomy, Clinical anatomy, Histology, Neuroanatomy, General anatomy and Embryology. Utilized innovative and modern methods of teaching techniques such as PBL, CBL TBL sessions to keep up higher standards in medical education & to promote students centered self-directed learning.



+92-3323671013



drahbaloch@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

English

Arabic

Malay

Urdu

EDUCATION

CHPE/CIMT (2020 ongoing)

University of Liverpool.

MIEE (2020-21)

Microsoft Education.

M.Phil Anatomy (2010)

Isra University Hyderabad

MBBS (1998)

Liaquat Medical College, Jamshoro

B.A (1996)

University of Sindh.

EXPERIENCE

Director e-LRC (2019-Date)

Frontier Medical and Dental College, ABT.

Professor (2019- Date)

Frontier Medical and Dental College, ABT.

Assot:Professor & Block coordinator(2015-19)

King Faisal University, Saudi Arabia.

Assot:Professor & Module coordinator(2013-14

Quest international University, Malaysia

Assistant Professor (2010-13)

Al-tibri Medical College, Karachi.

Lecturer (2002-2010)

Isra University, Hyderabad.

MY SKILLS







Microsoft office 365

Online Learning

Publications Research

HOBBIES





